《德古拉》前情回顾
Previously on Dracula...
Daniel！
Daniel!
…Alecander Grayson…我的一切…
...Alecander Grayson...the whole of my world...
Grayson
Grayson.
我为各位展现  无线能源
I give to you wireless power.
实验出现了一些技术难题  先生
Experiencing some technical difficulties, sir.
- 我发誓…  - 我们见过？
- I'd swear. - We've met?
没错  我也这样想
Yes, I was thinking the same thing.
我到底需要在黑暗中呆多久？
How long must I spend skulking in the shadows?
我想如常人一样在阳光下行走
I wanna walk in the sun like any other man.
先生  太阳
Sir, the sun.
见鬼
Damn.
你做我丈夫  我嫁你为妻
Be my husband, and I will be your wife.
- 你在想什么？  - 想你
- What are you thinking about?  - You.
我在想Jayne女士
I was thinking about Lady Jayne
当然  还有她那猎杀行动
Wetherby and her vampire hunting, of course.
现在先知死了
Now that the seers are dead,
那他召唤他的族类
he will much more easily
就更轻而易举了
attract others of his kind.
不久  伦敦就会斥满祸害
Soon, London will be crawling with the vermin.
Jayne女士是个猎人
Lady Jayne is a huntsman.
看来恶龙会
Seems the Ordo Draco is more
比我们预期的更有先见之明
forward-thinking than I gave it credit for.
诡异时光啊
Strange times.
相当诡异
Wonderfully strange.
- 你得杀了她  - 如果我杀了她
- You'll kill her. - If I kill her,
恶龙会只会找其他人取而代之
the Order will just send somebody else to replace her.
那你要断了你俩的联系
You'll end it with her.
我为什么要这样做？
Now why would I do that?
因为她是吸血鬼猎人
She's a vampire hunter.
Renfield  我要做的不仅是
Renfield, not only will
消除她仅有的怀疑
I evade her slightest suspicion,
还要拿走她从未给过别人的东西
I'll take from her a prize she's given no other man.
- 她的爱  - 不是
- Her love. - No.
比这更珍贵的…
Something far more precious...
她的信任
Her trust.
订两个明晚的位子
Make a reservation tomorrow night,
八点  Savoy酒店
8：00, for two at the Savoy.
对了  要主厅里最显眼的位子
The most exclusive, visible table in the main dining room.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
你好  主人
Hello, master.
根据腐烂情况来看
Given the extent of the putrefaction,
这个女性最年轻
I say the female is the youngest,
被转五年  甚至更少
five years sired, maybe less.
而另一方面  这一个
This one, on the other hand,
明显老得多
is clearly much older,
最少活了一世纪
a century undead at least.
就是说  这两个吸血鬼
I mean, that said, neither of the vampires
都不足以杀死先知
are old enough to be the ones that killed our seers.
那逃掉的那个呢？
But the one who eluded you?
我猜是他们的创造者
There, sire, I suspect,
比他们更年长
which would make him older still.
那是我们在寻找的吗？
Old enough to be the one we're searching for?
哦  他将是一个劲敌
Oh, he will be a formidable opponent.
- 劲敌？  - Browning先生  如果是
- formidable? - If so, Mr. Browning,
就只有上帝能帮助你了
then God help you,
因为如果连我都杀不了他
because if I can't kill the beast,
就没人可以了
no one can.
Josef Cervenka啊
Josef Cervenka.
我的得力右臂
My right hand.
也许吧
Maybe.
都过去很久了
A long time ago.
胡说
Nonsense.
你将再一次成为我手下战将
You are once more under my battlements.
召唤你来是有原因的  很快
I summoned you here for a reason, and very soon,
- 我们就会摧毁我们的宿敌  - 恶龙会？
- we shall destroy our greatest enemy. - The Ordo Draco?
对
The same.
我已经发现新的技术
Rich men who've bet their future on oil,
来摧毁
but I've discovered a technology
对石油孤注一掷的大亨们
that will destroy them.
- 但他们比以前更强大  - 说确切点
- But they are stronger than ever. Precisely.
就在今晚
Just this night,
我目睹我的两个幼类被猎人屠杀
I saw two of my brood slaughtered by a huntsman,
还是个女的
a female of all things.
所以我需要你的帮助
That's why I need your help.
我认识她
I know her.
那我们就把她抽筋削骨了
Then we will peel the flesh from her bones.
还不到时候
Not yet.
下饺子式的杀害不能将他们击败
We cannot defeat them by killing them one by one.
我们得直捣他们的权利之源
We must attack the source of their power.
他们的财富
Their wealth.
像寻常小偷那样偷走他们的钱包？
To pick their pockets like a common thief?
那样毫无尊严
There's no honor in that.
抱歉  先生  我听到动静
I'm sorry, sir. I heard voices.
Renfield  见见我的…
Renfield, this is my
老朋友  Josef Cervenka
old friend Josef Cervenka.
他想住这里多久
He will be staying in this house
就住多久
as long as he wishes.
—— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ——
出  品
翻译：火星人善良凡凡
翻译：幸福ing形式
翻译：依依yiyi
后期：飞越无限
监制：幸福ing形式
招贤纳士QQ群：233183580
—— 祝观影愉快 ——
—— 德 古 拉 ——
第一季 第四集
真让人吃惊
Such a shock.
小时候  Daniel就被诊断出心律紊乱
As a boy, Daniel was diagnosed with an irregular heartbeat.
我想发作  也只是时间问题罢了
I supposed it was just a matter of time before it gave out.
但是  这个年纪就死于心脏病
Still, he was so young
他还是太年轻了
to die of a heart attack.
也许我应该感谢上帝
Maybe I should just thank
让我们曾经相处那么久
the lord for the time we did have together.
我们要用牡丹和苹果花花环
We shall drape the walls and the ceiling
装扮墙壁和天花板
with garlands of peonies and apple blossoms.
你一下如何  Harker？
What do you think, Harker?
哦  只要Mina喜欢就好
Oh, whatever pleases Mina.
我想给她一个完美的订婚宴
I want this engagement party to be perfect for her.
谢谢你  Grayson先生  你确定…
Thank you, Mr. Grayson. Are you quite sure...
当然
Of course.
我很荣幸来主办你们的订婚宴
It'll be honor to host your engagement party.
还有大烛台
And candelabras.
随处可见的银质大烛台
Silver candelabras everywhere,
置于桌上
on the tables
点缀花饰
and in all the floral arrangements.
会有大烛台的
Candelabras it will be.
Mina？Mina  亲爱的  过来
Mina? Mina, darling, come here.
我来告诉你怎样出场
I want to show you how you're going to make your entrance.
马上回来
One moment.
告诉我
I want you to tell me
你是怎样看Arthur Ogilvy将军的
what you think about General Arthur Ogilvy.
他好像积极的
It seems he's the military's
支持对奥斯曼帝国开战
leading advocate for war against the Ottoman Empire.
- 只是表面现象而已  - 怎么说
- Well, appearances can be deceiving. - Explain.
私下里  他反对战争
In private, he opposes the war.
真正的好战分子是副将
The real advocate is his number two,
Colin Shaw将军  战争英雄
General Colin Shaw, the war hero.
深受公众拥护
Very popular in the public sphere.
额  这位战争英雄
Hmm, and yet this war hero
为了控制区域里的石油储备
is willing to spill
竟不惜血流成河
an ocean of blood to control the region's vast oil reserves.
但Shaw将军坚信奥斯曼是个威胁
But General Shaw believes the Ottomans are a real threat.
你该不会以为
You're not suggesting he's
他是为了个人利益而发动战争吧
advocating war for personal financial gain.
他是个傀儡
He's a puppet.
掌权者将身家性命
Powerful men have staked their fortunes
都压在了被视为未来燃料的石油上
on the presumption that the future will be fueled by oil.
看来他们不仅是对奥斯曼帝国宣战了
It seems they've not only declared
还想对Grayson能源下手
war on the Ottoman Empire, but on Grayson energy.
你和我
You and me
以及我们努力打拼的一切
and everything we worked so hard for.
抬头  Lucy
Head up, Lucy.
你不能只是走下楼梯  像滑的
You don't walk down the stairs, you glide.
我要你尽力查出
I want you to find out
关于这个Shaw将军的一切  Harker
everything you can about this General Shaw, Harker.
他的癖好   他的软弱
His weaknesses. His failures.
当然  除非  你还想
Unless, of course, you'd like
呆在这儿  讨论鲜花布置
to stay here and discuss floral arrangements.
交给我办吧
Leave it with me.
Mina
Mina.
你得从这儿入场
Make your entrance from down here.
烟花  餐前酒必须搭配烟花啊
Fireworks, we must have fireworks with our aperitifs.
Lucy  别说了
Lucy, do stop.
你会让Grayson先生后悔出此好意的
You'll make Mr. Grayson regret his hospitality.
- 胡说  - 准备好下一轮测试了
- Nonsense.- We're ready for another test run.
女士们  这是我的首席工程师
Ladies, this is my chief engineer,
Kowalski先生
Mr. Kowalski.
我等会儿就下去
I'll be down in a minute.
他是在说共振机吗？
Is he referring to the resonator machine?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
你在测试吗？ 只是些日常工作
- Are you testing it now? - Just routine.
如果你想要留下观看的话  没问题
If you'd like to stay and watch, you can.
哦 主啊 Mina 我们一定要看吗？
Oh, lord, Mina, must we?
Westernra小姐
Miss Westenra.
如果你想要离开  我可以帮你安排
If you wish to leave, I can easily arrange
给Murray小姐再加一辆马车
a second carriage for Miss Murray.
请和以往一样尽情享受
Enjoy, as always.
我以为所有事情都井然有条 Kowalski先生
I presume everything is in order, Mr. Kowalski.
开始第一阶段
Commence stage one.
第一阶段！
Stage one!
Mark！
Mark!
第二阶段！ Mark！
Stage two! Mark!
温度读数？
Temperature reading?
很稳定
Steady.
在预期值范围之内
Well inside specification.
上次聚会那晚
The night of the party,
你都可以在上面煎蛋了
you could've fried an egg on this.
啊！
Aah!
- 大家还好吗？ - 你没受伤吧？
- Is everyone okay? - Are you unhurt?
我们没事  我们没事
We're fine, we're fine.
发生了什么
What happened?
冷却系统工作很正常
The cooling system performed perfectly,
证明设计中的最薄弱的环节
illustrating the weakest link in the design.
就是铸造用的金属
The metal used for the casing.
Renfield
Renfield.
我会开始调查所有涉及镍铁合金的
I'll initiate a survey of all the British steel manufacturers
英帝国钢铁生产厂
that work with nickel-steel alloys.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不觉得螺丝和螺栓
I don't suppose nuts and bolts
能衡量你的股票
can measure up to your stock in trade.
你说什么？
Sorry?
为什么  鲜血和肉  当然了
Why, flesh and blood, of course.
没有什么比行医更高尚的了
There can be no higher calling than the practice of medicine.
能拯救生命
The ability to save lives
让我们的努力看起来微不足道
makes all our efforts here seem trivial.
谢谢你  Grayson先生
Thank you, Mr. Grayson.
是不是相似？
Resemblance?
不  她就是Ilona
No. She is Ilona.
我妻子四个世纪以前已经死了
My wife died four centuries ago.
我知道的  我那时在场
I know. I was there.
然后她转生
Then she has been born again,
命运把她带到您身边
and the fates have returned her to you.
现在  你给我听着  Josef
Now, you listen to me, Josef.
再也不许提
You must never again mention
Mina Murray和我妻子有多像了
Mina Murray's resemblance to my wife.
听懂了吗？
Do you understand me?
永远不要…对任何人讲
Never. To anyone.
- 你要去哪里？ - 出去
- Where are you going? - Out.
要不要来杯香槟打发时间？
Perhaps a glass of champagne to kill the time?
不  谢谢了
No, thank you.
多有趣的小惊喜
What a lovely surprise.
我以为你在花店那里
I'd expect you to be at the florist
选牡丹和苹果花呢
up to your neck in peonies and apple blossoms.
- 怎么了？  - 没事
- Is something wrong? - No.
听着  恩  我在重新考虑
Listen, um, I've been reconsidering the idea
要不要在Carfax庄园举办订婚宴
of having the engagement party at Carfax.
怎么了？
Why?
恩  我觉得不自在
Well, I-I feel uncomfortable.
开销很大
It's a huge imposition,
而且  老实说
and, well, frankly,
我不明白
I don't understand
Grayson先生这样做的动机是什么
Mr. Grayson's motives for hosting it.
我意思是
I mean,
毕竟你只是他的一名员工
you're just one of his employees after all.
我可没觉得自己就是个普通员工
Well, I'd like to think I'm a little more than just that.
恩  当然
Yes, of course.
我就是不知道为什么他如此…
I don't know why he's so interested in...
在意我们？
In us?
他如此乐于关注我们的事
He's assumed this very intense involvement
就好像…
in our relationship
他也是其中一员
as if he's a part of it somehow.
恩  那是因为
Well, that's because,
从某方面来说  他确实是
I suppose in a way, he is.
在我们分开的时候
When we split up,
是Grayson先生把我拉到一边
it was Mr. Grayson who took me aside
让我知道自己有多傻
and made me realize what a fool I was.
他让我认识你
He made me see you
并且尊重你本身
and respect you for who you are,
你不仅仅是一名妻子  母亲
not just a prospective wife and mother,
也是和我一样
but a woman with aspirations every bit
有追求的女性
as important as my own.
他真的这样？
He did that?
是啊
Yes.
我本不想告诉你的
I didn't wanna tell you.
听着  我知道你讨厌这些…
Look, I know you hate
繁文缛节
all of this bother over arrangements...
相当讨厌
Very much so.
那就让Lucy打理吧
So let Lucy handle them.
她就以此为生啊
She lives for it.
你所需要做的
All you have to do is
就是准时在宴会出现
turn up on time for the party.
那这段时间呢？
And in the meantime?
埋头工作
Bury yourself in work.
说的对
You're right.
说的没错
Of course you're right.
批完这些卷子后
Once you have graded those papers,
就去校储藏室
you will find in university
那儿有18只待宰羔羊
storage 18 recently slaughtered lambs.
把每只的海马体取出来
Extract the hippocampus from each
准备好了
and prepare them
给神经学的学生解剖课用
for dissection by the neurology students.
我几个小时后回来
I shall be back in a couple of hours.
别让我失望
Try not to disappoint me.
有问题吗？
Is there something wrong?
其实  我希望做点儿
Actually, I'd hoped for something
不这么乏味的事
a little less prosaic.
Mina  我们必须得打好根基
Now, now, Mina. We mustn't get ahead of ourselves.
宁做勤奋龟  不做偷懒兔  是吧？
Better to be the tortoise than the hare, yes?
只要不做羊就好
Anything but the lamb, I suppose.
这是什么巫术？
What is this witchcraft?
是科学
Science.
如果成功的话
If this works,
我们就能在阳光下活动
then we shall walk in daylight.
阳光下行走？
To walk in the sun?
你能想象吗  主人？
Can you imagine us, liege?
无论昼夜
Immortal,
不可战胜  永垂不朽
invincible by night and by day.
是的  是的  很激动人心  我确定
Yes, yes, it is all very thrilling, I'm sure.
（罗马尼亚语）干杯
Noroc.
我能感受到太阳
I can feel the sun.
我能感觉出温暖
I can feel its warmth.
主人
Master.
不
No.
Josef  不要
Josef. No.
是
Yes.
没错  起作用了
Yes, it worked.
这就算成功了？
You call this a success?
你没看到吗？
Don't you see?
它起作用了
It works, but only
不过就只在注射的组织部位
in the tissue surrounding the injection site.
没传运到心脏
Without a functioning heart,
药剂就没办法散布全身
the serum cannot be distributed throughout your body.
我们现在需要的
All we need now
就是一剂分散剂
is a dispersion agent.
不
No.
问题所在  是生理上的
The problem is one of mechanics,
而非化学问题
not chemistry.
心脏就只是一个泵
The heart is simply a pump,
其他一无是处
nothing more.
如果你能让我心脏运作起来
If we can make mine function,
问题就解决了  对吧？
the problem is solved, correct?
没错
Yes.
1880年
这些细胞是活的
These cells are alive.
所以呢？
So?
血细胞离体一小时就会死的
Blood cells die within an hour or so of extraction.
这个薄片是1887年的
This slide is dated 1887.
是九年前的了
That's nine years ago.
所以这是你为什么
And this is why you couldn't
不去花店见我的原因？
meet me at the florist?
太不可思议了
That makes no sense.
我真不明白
What I can't understand is
你怎么能对你的订婚宴
how you can maintain such a willful
这么不在乎呢
disinterest in your own engagement party.
什么？
What?
亲爱的Mina  有时和你说话
Honestly, Mina, it's like
就像和一个男人一样
talking to a man sometimes,
全心全意的
nose buried in whatever silly thing
埋头苦干那些无聊事儿
has captured his attention.
Lucy  怎么了？
Lucy, what's wrong?
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
Lucy  我…我不明白
Lucy, I-I don't understand.
你不会明白的
You wouldn't, would you?
你又不是那个一门心思
You're not the one attending to every detail
打理闺蜜奢华婚宴
for an extravagant party to celebrate the end of
每个细节的那个人
the only thing that's ever mattered to her.
- Lucy  - 真的
- Lucy.   - It's true.
一切都不同了
Things will never be the same.
我们永远是朋友啊
We will always be friends.
哦  Mina  亲爱的
Oh, Mina, darling.
你那么聪慧  却又如此愚钝
You are so terribly clever, yet so terribly stupid.
不  事实是你要结婚了
No, you are to be married, and that is that.
明白吗？
You understand?
不
No.
我不懂
I don't.
带上你的东西  咱去喝咖啡
Get your things. We'll go to the cafe.
太多事要讨论了
There's a million things to talk about.
对不起  先生
I am sorry, sir,
夫人马上就下来
I am assured my lady will be down presently.
那我一直等着
I have all the time in the world.
先生
Sir.
Grayson先生  真意外
Mr. Grayson. How unexpected.
我必须为昨天没去Savoy酒店而道歉
I must apologize for my absence from dinner at the Savoy.
虽然事不可免
It was as inexcusable
但也不可原谅
as it was unavoidable.
哦  拜托  我都忘了
Oh, please, I had forgotten about it entirely.
希望今晚可以有幸相伴
I was hoping I might make amends by
以作补偿
requesting the pleasure of your company this evening.
如果有什么
If there is one thing
让我特烦你们美国人的话
I find tiresome about you Americans,
那就是你们不懈的乐观精神了
it is your relentless optimism.
我保证你以后
I promise you a spectacle
会难忘今宵的
that you will not soon forget.
好了  Grayson先生
Come now, Mr. Grayson.
想当然  像你这种富人
Surely, a man of your affluence
很随意就能找一个晚餐伴侣
can find a dinner companion for the evening.
确实
Certainly.
只是这特别的娱乐项目
It's just that this particular diversion
普通女人可承受不了
is beyond the petty refinements of other women.
只有你有能力全然欣赏
Only you possess the sensibilities to appreciate it fully.
你这奉承也太明显了
Your flattery is too obvious.
奉承这种笨方法
Flattery is a dull blade that I
我是绝不会对你用的
would never employ against one such as yourself.
这活动  如果不能让我满意
This diversion, if it displeases me,
你就别再找我了
you will agree not to call on me ever again.
- 好  - 真的？
- Yes. - Really?
Elsa  厨佣
Elsa, from the kitchen.
哦  天啊
Oh, dear.
我想她没有近亲吧
I trust she has no close relatives.
和所有员工一样
Like all our staff,
没人会发现她不在了
none close enough to note her absence,
虽然我会想念她做的苹果蛋糕
though I will miss her apple crumb cakes.
该死的Cervenka
Bloody Cervenka.
我已经询问了Shaw将军麾下三人
I've interviewed three men from Shaw's regiment,
两个政敌
two political opponents and
一个被开了的军助
an adjunct who was dishonorably discharged,
没人说一句坏话
and none had a bad word to say.
你好像很失望
You sound disappointed.
不  我没失望
No, I'm not disappointed.
我只是不明白
It's just I don't understand
为什么Grayson对此感兴趣
why Grayson's so interested.
我是说  坦白讲
I mean, frankly,
我从小就很仰慕Shaw将军
I've admired Shaw since I was a boy.
上学的时候
I actually chose him
我还拿他当传记研究对象
for a subject for a biography in school.
想知道一些相当奇怪的事吗？
Do you wanna know something very, very odd?
什么？
What?
从我最近做的调查来看
For all my recent digging,
只说明一件事儿
I've not been able to uncover one single fact
就是并没什么发现
that I didn't include back then.
也许本就没什么可说的
Perhaps there is nothing more to tell.
也许吧
- That's why. - Perhaps.
告诉我  Szabo
Tell me something, Szabo.
你见过没有任何秘密的人吗？
Have you ever met a man without any secrets?
上周我自己
I've destroyed over half
就杀了不止六个吸血鬼
a dozen Nosferatu in the last week alone,
他们都是被主人召唤的
and they are summoned by their sire.
我…我知道你对那个美国人的顾虑
Now, I-I share your concerns about the American,
但他现在不是我们面对的最大威胁
but he is hardly the greatest threat that we face.
同意  但我们也别低估了Grayson
Agreed, but we must not underestimate Grayson
还有他的财力
nor the power of his purse.
尽管Harker和他
Making inroads with his man Harker
只是个开始
is a start, but nonetheless.
没错  我认为Grayson值得查下
Yes, I think Grayson does bear scrutiny.
Jayne说的对
I agree with Jayne.
就不劳组织动手了
The Order needn't be involved.
我会派人盯着的
I shall see to it personally.
很好  有消息通知我
Good. Keep me informed.
啊  我们的贵客来了
Ah, our distinguished guests have arrived.
欢迎啊  Shaw将军  Ogilvy将军
Welcome, General Shaw, General Ogilvy.
夫人  大人
My lady. My lord.
有请  先生们  请坐
Please, gentlemen, sit down.
那么  将军
So, general,
您保证过在三月份
you assured us total control of
就能完全掌控波斯油田
the Persian oil fields by March.
对  没错  但你也知道
Yes, of course, but as you may know,
情况变得略微复杂了
the situation has become much more complex.
何以见得？  愿闻其详
How so? Please explain.
- 我能？ - 当然
- May I? - Of course.
自从苏丹颁布了法令
Our provocateurs have been
规定退斩无赦
unable to foment so much as a border skirmish
我们的卧底就不能
since the sultan issued a decree
随意煽动边境冲突了
to his men to stand down under pain of death.
所以你也瞧见了
So you see,
发动先发制人的全面入侵
there's little we can do,
我们无能为力
save a full-scale preemptive invasion.
当然  议会也绝不会…
Of course, parliament would never...
深表遗憾  Show将军
My condolences, General Shaw.
什么?
I'm sorry?
Ogilvy将军上吊自杀了
It appears General Ogilvy hanged himself.
他的属下明天早晨
His adjunct will discover him
会在他房间的浴室发现他的尸体
in the washroom of his quarters tomorrow morning.
真悲哀
Tragic.
那么将军  我们什么时候
So, general, when can we expect
能开始进攻奥斯曼帝国?
to begin the Ottoman offensive?
八月怎么样?
Shall we say August?
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
就八月
August.
这案子很有趣
It is an interesting case,
需要发挥你的特殊才能
one which requires your particular talents.
你的目的是什么?
What are your intentions?
找到Alexander Grayson在这世上的
Discover the one thing Mr. Alexander Grayson
一件挚爱之物
loves most in all the world.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
腐化它  毁坏它
Corrupt it. Deface it.
将它从世上抹去
Obliterate it from this earth.
组织知道你的计划吗?
Is the Order aware of your intention?
他们知道我在调查Grayson先生
They're aware that I'm investigating Mr. Grayson.
请回答我的问题
Please. Answer the question.
你和我一样清楚他们会怎样
Well, you know as well as I that if they did,
我会被逼解释我的动机
I would be forced to explain my motivation.
你是说
You mean your son's recent suicide
你儿子殉情自杀?
after the death of his lover?
拜托  Kleiberson女士
Please, Miss Kleiberson.
我只是想澄清事实
I only wish to clarify the situation,
那就是…
and that is thus...
你想利用我
You wish to employ my services
来执行未经批准的行动
in order to execute an unsanctioned operation.
我说过  并非完全未经批准
As I said before, not completely unsanctioned.
我明白了
I understand.
那这件事上
May I then rely on your
我可否完全信赖您会保守秘密
complete discretion in this matter
好让我另寻合伙人呢?
so that I may engage another contractor?
不必要
That will not be necessary.
我决定接手这个案子
I have decided to accept the assignment.
就算未经批准?
Despite it being unsanctioned?
正因为没经批准
Because it is unsanctioned,
我要求双倍酬劳
I will require double my standard fee.
当然  包括支出
Plus expenses, of course.
没问题
Of course.
Harker先生吗?
Mr. Harker?
欲知Show真相  四轮马车接头
今晚九点  前来见我
似乎贵夫人今晚想见我
It seems Her Ladyship wishes to see me tonight.
详情未知
No details.
真有趣
How intriguing.
先生  Cervenka先生还要在这儿呆多久?
Sir, how long is Mr. Cervenka going to be our guest?
我说了
You heard me.
随便他
As long as he wishes.
你有意见?
Do you have any objections?
是的
Oh, yes,
很多意见…
quite a growing number of objections...
最主要的是他缺乏谨慎
Chief among which is his lack of discretion
完全没自制力
and complete absence of self-control.
没错
You're right.
他很冲动
He can be impetuous.
但Josef在战场上
But Josef has saved my life on the battlefield
救过我无数次
more times than I care to count.
他与我情同兄弟
He's like my brother,
胜似兄弟
more than my brother.
他的忠诚毋庸置疑
His loyalty is absolute,
也对我绝对服从
and he will obey my orders.
尽管如此
Nevertheless, he has demonstrated
他的服从和忠诚
that his obedience and loyalty fall
与他的本性相去甚远
a distant second and third to his nature.
他不能被驯服
He cannot be domesticated,
不能完全信任
nor fully trusted.
为什么?
Why?
其一  他知道你对Murray女士的情意
He knows your true feelings toward Miss Murray, for one,
且知道其中渊源
and their origins.
我已经让他发誓保守秘密
I've sworn his silence.
我相信他会保守秘密
A silence I'm sure he means to keep,
只是不知道他能保守多久
but only insofar as he's capable of keeping it.
我担忧的不是他的忠诚
It's not his loyalty that worries me.
真高兴你能来
I'm glad you came.
这些最好亲自处理
These things are best done in person.
什么?
What things?
我对昨晚的宴会很开心
Well, I did enjoy our soiree last night,
你的陪伴
and I do find your company,
也让人十分愉悦
on occasion, most agreeable,
但我必须结束这段关系
but I'm afraid I must terminate this relationship.
早预料到了这悲惨的一幕
How distressingly predictable.
- 你说什么?  - 没什么
- Excuse me? - Never mind.
- 我先走了  - 不  等等
- I'll be on my way. - No, wait.
我很好奇
I'm curious.
你为什么觉得预料的这一幕
Exactly what is this predictability
- 如此...   - 悲伤吗?
- that you find so... - Distressing?
比起悲伤  更觉得是失望
Well, not so much distressing as disappointing.
真的?
Really?
情况很清楚
The situation is clear,
事实上  显而易见
crystal clear, in fact.
- 要我继续说下去?  - 请讲
- Must I go on? - Please do.
你是一个以驯服男人
You're a woman who takes great pleasure
为乐的女人
in asserting her domination over men.
然而  一旦驯服
However, once you do,
你就对他们失去兴趣
you very soon grow bored with them.
讲得很对  继续
True enough. Go on.
自我们相遇
Since we met, you've made every effort
你就想方设法驯服我
to do the same with me,
然而你却彻底失败了
and in this, you have utterly failed.
噢
Oh.
未能成功驯服我
This failure to dominate me
使你对我感到迷恋
has led to you being infatuated with me.
而这强烈的情感
Such is the intensity of your emotions
威胁到了你的独立与控制欲
that they threaten your sense of independence and control.
而再次掌握控制的唯一途径
The only way to reassert this control
就是结束我们的关系
is by terminating our relationship.
你太自恋了
Oh, you do flatter yourself so.
你想要结束关系
Your vulnerability is evident
就暴露了你的脆弱
by your withdrawal.
这样做真的很怯懦
I call your actions cowardice.
瞧你这无聊的论调
I call your ploys tedious.
你依然认为你对我毫无感觉?
You still assert that you feel nothing for me?
完全没有
Nothing at all.
先生  跟我来
Follow me, sir.
- 先生  这边  - 今晚的约会对象?
- This way, sir. - Tonight's engagement?
没错
I imagine so.
他来的时候看到我也在
And does it give you great pleasure
你是不是很高兴?
to see me here as he arrives?
Grayson先生  游戏…
The game, Mr. Grayson,
都需要至少三个玩家
requires at least three players.
总有一天  夫人
Someday, madam,
你会发现我不是玩玩而已
you'll realize I was never playing.
女猎人玩弄了你
The huntress made a fool of you.
你知道什么
You know nothing.
我跟踪了你
I followed you.
每个字听得真真切切
I heard every word.
谁允许你跟踪我的?
Who gave you permission to follow me?
昨晚你回来的时候
I could smell her stink on you
我就闻到了她的臭味
when you returned home last night.
我真不敢相信
I could never have believed you would consort
你竟和这样可鄙的生物交往
with such a despicable creature.
你不明白吗?
Do you not understand?
我们的策略非常复杂
We have a very complex strategy.
其中会有些让人不爽
Some of our tactics are distasteful.
- 是恶心  - 也许吧
- Disgusting. - Perhaps.
但如果想胜利
But they are necessary
就必须这样做
if we are to emerge victorious.
我们在玩一场危险
We are playing a very dangerous
而不可饶恕的游戏
and a very unforgiving game.
引诱他们的女猎人
By seducing their huntress,
把她从游戏中剔除
I take her out of their game.
但这样行不通了
Ah, but not anymore
因为她
because there she is,
回到游戏中了
back on the board,
追捕我们  杀害我们
hunting us, killing us.
你不记得我们是猎人
Do you not remember when we were the hunters
他们是猎物的时候了吗?
and they were the prey?
我们是怎样在早餐前
Why, you and I
就捕获上百的猎物
would harvest a hundred souls before breakfast.
我的君主啊
Please, my liege.
我恳求您  让我杀了她
I beseech thee. Let me kill her.
让她惨叫
Make her scream.
Harker先生?
Mr. Harker?
你把便条给我的?
You sent me the note?
我叫Peter Lang
Peter Lang,
曾是女王陛下步枪旅下士
formally Corporal Lang of Her Majesty's rifle brigade.
你知道Shaw的底细?
You have the truth I seek regarding Shaw?
是的  给我十块才告诉你
I do. Cost you 10 bob to hear it.
我这有个地址
I've got an address for you and a name,
以及Vera Markham这名字
a lady called Vera Markham.
她和他什么关系?
Who is she to him?
你自己去查吧
See for yourself.
是谁?
Who is it?
我是Jonathan Harker
Uh, my name's Jonathan Harker.
什么事?
Yes?
我找Vera Markham
I'm looking for Vera Markham.
我就是
I'm Vera Markham.
噢  天啊  噢  我的天哪
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
- 你的心...  - 刚有个男人
- Your heart... - There was a man.
不  不  他走了
No, no, he's gone,
他走了  已经走了
he's gone, he's gone.
他走了  你把他吓走了
He's gone. You scared him away.
噢  天哪  噢  你救了我
Oh, God. Oh, you saved my life.
你刚在我卧室干什么?
What were you doing in my bedroom in the first place?
我有时失眠
I suffer from insomnia from time to time,
习惯夜里散步
and it's my habit to take long, nighttime walks.
近来  发现自己很喜欢
As of late, I find myself
在这条街上走
increasingly drawn to this street.
这是我们要找的人?
The one we've been searching for?
我想是的
I believe so.
所以伦敦再次解放了?
So London is free again?
干得好
Excellent.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
尽管是用的你的方法
Your methods, though.
但你的方法太鲁莽蛮干了
It was reckless, foolhardy, even,
甚至把它引诱到你家里
to lure such a creature into your home.
- 会不会有可能他...   - 不会的
- There was every chance he... - There was no chance.
- 但你得...  - 没机会
- But surely you must see... - There was no chance.
你不会认出她的
You would not have recognized her.
潜心悔过
So contrite,
温柔可人
so gentle,
腼腆羞涩
so shy.
我驯服她了
I have sheared the tiger's claws.
正如您所说  先生
Just as you said you would, sir.
尽管有人怀疑过我
Although some doubted me.
她再也看不见我了
She'll never see me now.
恶龙会已经失去最强的武器
The Ordo Draco has lost its most dangerous weapon,
却还不知情
and it doesn't even know it.
而你也一道儿处理了Josef
And you were able to remove Josef in the process.
妙哉
A masterstroke.
没错
Yes.
- 对不起  先生  - 没关系
- I'm sorry, sir. - Don't mention it.
Josef是一名士兵
Josef was a soldier.
他会明白的
He would have understood.
有时  你必须牺牲骑士
Sometimes, you have to sacrifice a knight
才能俘获女王
to capture a queen.
Josef  再见
Good-bye, Josef.
明天  Renfield  我们回去工作
Tomorrow, we get back to work, Renfield.
我们需要共鸣器的合金
We need that alloy for the resonator.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
夫人  我来帮您
Ma'am, may I help you with that?
什么…
Wha...
我们是警察  他是罪犯
Police business. He's a known criminal.
不必恐慌
No cause for alarm.
快点儿  快离开这儿
Come on, let's get out of here.